{
    "subject": "resource/Karl_Theodor_Menke",
    "predicate": "property/deathDate",
    "object": "1861",
    "human_readable": "Karl Theodor Menke died in 1861.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8755288124084473,
            "question": "When did Karl Theodor Menke die?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6962935924530029,
            "question": "What was the cause of Karl Theodor Menke's death?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6884185671806335,
            "question": "Who was Karl Theodor Menke?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6391414403915405,
            "question": "Is there any further context surrounding Karl Theodor Menke's death?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5137296319007874,
            "question": "Was Karl Theodor Menke a historical figure?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.42342665791511536,
            "question": "What year is significant in relation to Karl Theodor Menke?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.39410462975502014,
            "question": "What information do we have about Karl Theodor Menke's life?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.39276254177093506,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about Karl Theodor Menke?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.33252716064453125,
            "question": "Were there any notable events happening in 1861?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.31321799755096436,
            "question": "Can you provide details about Karl Theodor Menke's profession or accomplishments?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Karl Theodor Menke died in 1861.",
            "html": "dbpedia_781_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Were there any notable events happening in 1861?",
            "html": "dbpedia_781_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me more about Karl Theodor Menke?",
            "html": "dbpedia_781_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What information do we have about Karl Theodor Menke's life?",
            "html": "dbpedia_781_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_781_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_781_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_781_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_781_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_781_65.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_781_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_781_73.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_781_75.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_781_78.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_781_79.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer:\n\n`{'output': 'yes'}`\n\nThe document at file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_781/re-ranker-msmarco/79.txt mentions that Karl Theodor Menke was born on September 13, 1791 and died in 1861."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe information provided in the documents states that Karl Theodor Menke (September 13, 1791 - 1861) lived until 1861, which supports the statement that he died in 1861."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}